Garrison Family Papers, 1694-2005 (bulk 1830-1950)
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES VII. PHOTOGRAPHS 1839-1998
  - Friends and associates
    - C 1886-1930, undated, [See also Oversize Materials] (Box 205, Folder 13)
    - Chaceundated (Box 205, Folder 14)
    - Chapman, Maria Weston 1905 (Box 205, Folder 15)
    - Chase 1862-63, undated (Box 205, Folder 16)
    - Clark family
      - Groups 1898-1959 (Box 205, Folder 17)
      - Individuals 1898-1947, undated, [See also Oversize Materials] (Box 205, Folder 18)
    - Conant Lucy Scarborough 1886-92, undated (Box 205, Folder 19)
    - Conway, Moncure D. 1863-97, undated (Box 205, Folder 20)
    - D 1881, undated (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Davis
      - Edward M. 1871, undated (Box 206, Folder 2)
      - Maria Mottundated (Box 206, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous 1892, undated (Box 206, Folder 4)
    - Dennis 1875, undated (Box 206, Folder 5)
    - Douglass, Frederickundated (Box 206, Folder 6)
    - E 1914, undated (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Edison, Thomas A.undated (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - Edward VII and VIIIundated (Box 206, Folder 9)
    - Eliot, Georgeundated (Box 206, Folder 10)
    - Emerson, Ralph Waldo 1878, [See also Oversize Materials] (Box 206, Folder 11)
    - Fundated, [See also Oversize Materials] (Box 206, Folder 12)
    - Fowlds, George F. 1914 (Box 206, Folder 13)
    - Fremont John and Jessie Benton 1891, undated (Box 206, Folder 14)
    - G 1884-1916, undated, [See also Cased images] (Box 206, Folder 15)
    - George, Henry 1896-97, undated (Box 206, Folder 16)
    - Gladstone, William E.undated (Box 206, Folder 17)
    - Grimké, Angelina 1879 (Box 206, Folder 18)
    - H 1873-1942, undated (Box 206, Folder 19)
    - Hallundated, [See also Cased images] (Box 206, Folder 20)
    - Hallowell
      - Anna Davisundated, [See also Cased images] (Box 206, Folder 21)
      - Miscellaneous 1842-98, undated (Box 206, Folder 22)
    - Hollingsworth, Roseundated (Box 206, Folder 23)
    - Holmes, Oliver Wendellundated (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - Hooker, Isabella Beecher 1888-1903 (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - Hopper 1863-92 (Box 207, Folder 3)
    - I-J 1882-85, undated (Box 207, Folder 4)
    - Jefferson, Joseph 1902, undated, [See also Garrison, Francis Jackson] (Box 207, Folder 5)
    - Johnsonundated (Box 207, Folder 6)
    - K-L 1890-1926, undated (Box 207, Folder 7)
    - Lincoln, Abrahamundated, [See Oversize Materials] (Box 207)
    - Linden, Josephcirca 1890 (Box 207, Folder 8)
    - Lippincott, Sara Jane Clarkundated (Box 207, Folder 9)
    - Livermore, Mary A. 1901 (Box 207, Folder 10)
    - Livingston, Mabel Wright 1890, undated (Box 207, Folder 11)
    - Longfellow, Henry, [See Flat File]
    - Lowell, James Russellundated (Box 207, Folder 12)
    - M 1860-1961, undated (Box 207, Folder 13)
    - Mayundated (Box 207, Folder 14)
    - McKim 1881-86, undated, [See also Cased images] (Box 207, Folder 15)
    - Morse, Lucy Gibbons, [See Garrison, Ellen Wright]
    - Mott, [See also Cased images]
      - Lucretia Coffin 1875-79, undated (Box 207, Folder 16)
      - Jamesundated (Box 207, Folder 17)
      - Marianna Pelhamundated, [See also Family-Wright family] (Box 207, Folder 18)
      - May, undated (Box 207, Folder 19)
      - Miscellaneousundated (Box 207, Folder 20)
    - N 1857-99, undated (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - Norton 1871, undated, [See also Family--Charles Dyer Norton- Norton family] (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - Osborne
      - Eliza 1873-95, undated (Box 208, Folder 3)
      - Family
        - Groups 1872, undated (Box 208, Folder 4)
        - Individuals 1861-1902, undated, [See Cased images] (Box 208, Folder 5)
    - Osgood, Samuelundated, [See Oversize Materials]
    - P 1839-64, 1926, undated, [See also Oversize Materials] (Box 208, Folder 6)
    - Pankhurst, Emmelineundated (Box 208, Folder 7)
    - Parker, Theodore and Lydia Cabotundated, [See also Oversize Materials] (Box 208, Folder 8)
    - Parrish 1880, undated (Box 208, Folder 9)
    - Phillips, Wendell 1845, undated, [See also Cased images] (Box 208, Folder 10)
    - Pompelli, Elise, [See Linden, Joseph]
    - Purvis, Hattie and Robert 1833, undated (Box 208, Folder 11)
    - Quincy, Edmundundated (Box 208, Folder 12)
    - R 1878, undated (Box 208, Folder 13)
    - Renwick 1868, undated (Box 208, Folder 14)
    - Robinson, Edward 1895, undated (Box 208, Folder 15)
    - S 1860-1965, undated, [See also Oversize Materials] (Box 208, Folder 16)
    - Severance
      - Caroline 1890-1903, undated, [See also Subjects-Suffrage-Groups] (Box 208, Folder 17)
      - T.C.undated (Box 208, Folder 18)
    - Seward 1866, undated (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - Shaw
      - Emily Mott 1873, undated (Box 209, Folder 2)
      - Frankundated (Box 209, Folder 3)
    - Smith
      - Joseph 1885-94, undated (Box 209, Folder 4)
      - Gerritundated (Box 209, Folder 5)
    - Spring, Rebecca, [See Subjects-Suffrage-Groups]
    - Stone, Lucy 1893, undated (Box 209, Folder 6)
    - Stowe, Harriet Beecherundated (Box 209, Folder 7)
    - Sumner, Charlesundated, [See also Flat File] (Box 209, Folder 8)
    - T 1861, undated (Box 209, Folder 9)
    - Tauriton, Kae Dexter Ware 1893-99, undated (Box 209, Folder 10)
    - Taft, William Howard, [See Family-Charles Dyer Norton]
    - Taylor, Zachary1914? (Box 209, Folder 11)
    - Terry, Ellenundated (Box 209, Folder 12)
    - Thoreau, Henry Davidundated (Box 209, Folder 13)
    - Tolstoy, Leoundated (Box 209, Folder 14)
    - Tubman, Harrietundated (Box 209, Folder 15)
    - V-W 1875-1917, [See also Cased images] (Box 209, Folder 16)
    - Waltonundated (Box 209, Folder 17)
    - Washington, Booker T.undated (Box 209, Folder 18)
    - Webb, Alfred 1889, undated (Box 209, Folder 19)
    - Webster, Daniel 1849, undated (Box 209, Folder 20)
    - Weld, Theodore Dwight 1892-93, undated (Box 209, Folder 21)
    - Whittier, John Greeleafundated (Box 209, Folder 22)
    - Wills, Charlotte, [See Subjects-Suffrage-Groups] (Box 209)
    - Yale, Johnundated (Box 209, Folder 23)
    - Yarnellundated (Box 209, Folder 24)
    - Young, Brighamundated (Box 209, Folder 25)
    - Zarate, Luciaundated (Box 209, Folder 26)
    - Unidentified, undated
      - Groups 1896-1992, undated (Box 210, Folder 1)
      - Individuals
        - Men 1896-1992, undated (Box 210, Folder 2-3)
        - Women 1921-26, undated (Box 210, Folder 4)
  - Subjects
    - Abolition
      - Groups
        - Ambleside 1889, undated (Box 211, Folder 1)
        - Executive Board of the Pennsylvania Anti-Slavery Society 1851 (Box 211, Folder 2)
        - Lucy Stone's House 1886, undated (Box 211, Folder 3)
      - Slave childrenundated (Box 211, Folder 4)
      - Underground railroadundated (Box 211, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneousundated (Box 211, Folder 6)
    - Auburn contemporaries of Martha Coffin Wrightundated (Box 211, Folder 7)
    - Barnstable (MA) beachundated (Box 211, Folder 8)
    - British political figuresundated (Box 211, Folder 9)
    - Cemeteries 1886, 1890s (Box 211, Folder 10)
    - Dwarfsundated (Box 211, Folder 11)
    - Garrison Wool Shop (164 Congress Street, Boston, MA) 1874 (Box 211, Folder 12)
    - Houses and vacation places, [See also Oversize Materials]
      - Bensonundated (Box 211, Folder 13)
      - Coffin-Mott
        - Fair St.undated (Box 211, Folder 14)
        - Nantucketundated (Box 211, Folder 15)
        - Roadsideundated (Box 211, Folder 16)
      - Garrison
        - Boston (MA)
          - 1763 Beacon St., circa 1890 (Box 211, Folder 17)
          - Dix Placeundated (Box 211, Folder 18)
        - Brookline (MA)undated (Box 211, Folder 19)
        - Dobb's Ferry (NY) Thorwood 1880, undated (Box 211, Folder 20)
        - Duxbury (MA) 1950s (Box 211, Folder 21)
        - Lincoln (MA)
          - David Lloyd Garrison house 1990s (Box 211, Folder 22)
          - Edith Stephenson Garrison house 1964-70, undated (Box 211, Folder 23)
        - Moon Hill Camp, Pottersville, NYundated (Box 211, Folder 24)
        - Newburyport (MA)undated (Box 211, Folder 25)
        - Roxbury (MA), [See also Oversize Materials]
          - Cedar Streetundated (Box 211, Folder 26)
          - Rockledge 1876-91, undated (Box 211, Folder 27)
        - Santa Barbara (CA) 1963-65 (Box 211, Folder 28)
        - West Newton (MA)
          - 103 Prince Streetundated (Box 212, Folder 1)
          - 65 Sterling Street 1915-34, undated (Box 212, Folder 2)
        - Wianno, Cape Cod (MA), [See also Oversize Materials]
          - The Cones 1879-80s, undated (Box 212, Folder 3)
          - Cotocheset house 1883-1911, undated, [See also Wianno Club] (Box 212, Folder 4)
          - Edgewood 1901, undated (Box 212, Folder 5)
          - First Pond 1963, undated (Box 212, Folder 6)
          - Hallowell Cottage 1885-1918, undated (Box 212, Folder 7)
          - Old Hundredsundated (Box 212, Folder 8)
          - Pagan Point 1927-47, undated (Box 212, Folder 9)
          - Rich Cottage 1911, undated (Box 212, Folder 10)
          - Wayside1181-1963, undated (Box 212, Folder 11)
          - Wianno Club (formerly Cotocheset house)circa 1900-63 (Box 212, Folder 12)
          - Scenes
            - Bathers 1880s, undated (Box 212, Folder 13)
            - Wianno Beachundated (Box 212, Folder 14)
            - Watercolors of Osterville 1880s, undated (Box 212, Folder 15)
            - Miscellaenous 1897, undated (Box 212, Folder 16)
        - Miscellaneous 1909-74, undated (Box 213, Folder 1)
      - Stephensonundated (Box 213, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous
        - Identified 1901-48, undated (Box 213, Folder 3)
        - Unidentifiedundated (Box 213, Folder 4)
    - Unidentified lithographs by Gustav Kruellundated, [See also Oversize Materials] (Box 213, Folder 5)
    - Minstrelsundated (Box 213, Folder 6)
    - Nantucketundated (Box 213, Folder 7)
    - Suffrage, [See also Family-Garrison, Eleanor]
      - Groupscirca 1890, 1896 (Box 213, Folder 8)
      - New York suffragists in "farmerette" costumescirca 1915 (Box 213, Folder 9)
      - Parades 1913-17 (Box 213, Folder 10)
    - Theosophy 1903-05 (Box 213, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Unidentified scenesundated (Box 213, Folder 12)
      - Identified 1900-64, undated (Box 213, Folder 13)
  - Albums
    - Wianno 1898 (Box 214, Folder 1)
    - William Lloyd Garrison 1902 and Claire ("Tita") Garrisoncirca 1903 (Box 214)
    - MaurometJune 1901 (Box 214)
    - Trip to Europe 1926 (Box 214, Folder 2)
    - Edith S. Garrison trip to Pasedena, Pebble Beach, and Tita's family 1932 (Box 214, Folder 3)
    - World War II [ Negative albums of David Lloyd Garrison] 1940s (Box 214, Folder 4)
    - Wianno 1940s-early 1950s (Box 214, Folder 5)
    - Edith S. Garrison photographs of grandchildren, Wianno, and family photographsearly 1900s-1968, undated (Box 214, Folder 6-7)
    - Edith S. Garrison, photographs of family and friends 1960s, undated (Box 214, Folder 8)
    - Edith S. Garrison, Lincoln home 1965-68, undated (Box 214, Folder 9)
    - Garrison familycirca 1860s-70s (Box 215, Folder 1)
    - Celebrities 1860-70s (Box 215, Folder 2-3)
    - William Lloyd Garrison (1805)circa mid-late 19th century (Box 216)
    - William Lloyd Garrison (1838)1877 (Box 216)
    - Stephenson familycirca 1880s (Box 217)
    - Sterling Street and Wianno 1915 (Box 218)
    - Pagan Point 1944 (Box 218)
    - "Illustrations and inspirational" [David Lloyd Garrison] 1920s (Box 218)
    - Children of William Lloyd Garrison 1874, 1901-14 (Box 219)
    - Bird and egg photographs [by David Lloyd Garrison?] 1919-20 (Box 219)
    - Ames family in England, France, and Italy 1922 (Box 219)
    - David, Faith, Yoy, and Tita in England 1926 (Box 219)
    - David Lloyd Garrison, World War II 1942-45 (2v) (Box 220)
    - Family of William Lloyd Garrison 1874, 1886-1962 (Box 221)
  - Cased Images
    - Large frames
      - Garrison William Lloyd (1805), [W.R. Hallowell?], and unidentified abolitionist (daguerreotype)undated (Box 222)
      - Garrison, William Lloyd and Wendell Phillips (daguerreotype)undated (Box 222)
    - Medium frames (tintypes)
      - Wright, William, Ellen, and Frank 1857 (Box 223)
      - Wright, Frank and Ellen 1858 (Box 223)
      - Wright, Frank, Ellen, William, and Eliza 1861 (Box 223)
      - Wright, Frank Pellam and Martha Coffin 1861 (Box 223)
      - Wright, Frank, Ellen and, William 1861 (Box 223)
    - Small frames
      - Garrison, Elizabeth "Lizzie" Pease (daguerreotype) 1848 (2 copies) (Box 224, Folder 1-2)
      - Wright, Martha, and William (daguerreotype)circa 1850 (Box 224, Folder 3)
      - Wright, Matthew Tallman, (daguerreotype)circa 1850 (Box 224, Folder 4)
      - Wright, Ellen, and Alice Hall, (tintype)circa early 1850s (Box 224, Folder 5)
      - Wright, Martha, and Ellen (daguerreotype)circa mid-1850s (Box 224, Folder 6)
      - Wright, Ellen, and Florence Osborne (tintype)circa 1856 (Box 225, Folder 1)
      - Wright, Frank, and Ellen (daguerreotype)circa 1856 (Box 225, Folder 2)
      - Gould, Amelia, (daguerreotype) 1857 (Box 225, Folder 3)
      - Garrison, Wendell P. (daguerreotype) 1857 (Box 225, Folder 4)
      - Wright, Ellen, (tintype) circa late 1850s (Box 225, Folder 5)
      - Brewoort, Alice (tintype) 1861 (Box 225, Folder 6)
      - Quincy, Miss, (tintype) 1861 (Box 225, Folder 7)
      - Garrison, William Lloyd (1838), (daguerreotype)5 Aug 1861 [2 copies] (Box 226, Folder 1-2)
      - Garrison, Charles Anthony (daguerreotype)circa 1870s/80s (Box 226, Folder 3)
      - Garrison, Annie Dennis McKim (daguerreotype)undated (Box 226, Folder 4)
      - Garrison, Charles Follen (tintype)undated (Box 226, Folder 5)
      - McKim, James Miller and Sarah A. Speakman (tintype)undated (Box 226, Folder 6)
      - Garrison, Lucy McKim, (tintype)undated (Box 227, Folder 1)
      - McKim, Miller (daguerreotype)undated (Box 227, Folder 2)
      - Mott, Emily (daguerreotype)undated (Box 227, Folder 3)
      - Mott, Lucretia Coffin (daguerreotype)undated (Box 227, Folder 4)
      - Mott, Marianna Pelham (daguerreotype)undated (Box 227, Folder 5)
      - Pellham, William (daguerreotype)undated (Box 227, Folder 6)
      - Wright, David (ambrotype)undated (Box 227, Folder 7)
      - Wright, David (daguerreotype)undated (Box 228, Folder 1)
      - Garrison, Ellen Wright, (tintype)undated (Box 228, Folder 2)
      - Wright, Martha Coffin (ambrotype)undated (Box 228, Folder 3)
      - Wright, Martha Coffin (daguerreotype)undated (Box 228, Folder 4)
      - Wood, Charles P. (ambrotype)undated (Box 228, Folder 5)
      - Wood, Charles P. (daguerreotype)undated (Box 228, Folder 6)
      - Unidentified young child, (tintype)undated (2 copies) (Box 228, Folder 7)
  - Oversize Photographs
    - Garrison
      - Charles 1891 (Box 229)
      - David Lloydcirca 1920s-40s (Box 229)
      - Edith Stephenson. 1937 (Box 229)
      - Helen Benson
        - Photographundated (Box 229)
        - Paintingundated (Box 229)
      - Lucy McKim (Gustav Kruell lithograph)undated (Box 229)
      - Wendell P.undated (includes Gustav Kruell lithograph) (Box 230)
      - William Lloyd (1805)
        - Photographs 1854-73, undated (Box 230)
        - Paintings (Box 230)
      - William Lloyd (1838)1899-1900, undated (Box 230)
      - William Lloyd (1874) in group photographs1892-97, undated (Box 231)
    - Harwood, Faith Garrison 1918-34 (Box 231)
    - Villard, Fanny Garrison 1881 (Box 231)
    - Miscellaneous family group photographs
      - Thanksgiving 1886 (Box 231)
      - Wedding of Frank W. Garrison and Mildred Yarnell 1900 (Box 231)
      - Eleanor S. Garrison, William Lloyd Garrison (1902), Tita, and David Lloyd Garrison1907 (Box 231)
      - John B. and David Lloyd Garrisoncirca 1920s (Box 231)
    - Friends and associates
      - John Quincy Adamsundated (Box 232)
      - Cinque, Joseph (leader of Amistad revolt)undated (Box 232)
      - Clark, W. S. 1912 (Box 232)
      - Coffin, Thomasundated (Box 232)
      - Emerson, Ralph Waldo 1882 (Box 232)
      - Folger, Anna. undated (Box 232)
      - Lincoln, Abraham, (Gustav Kruell lithograph) 1891 (Box 232)
      - Osgood, Samuelundated (Box 232)
      - Paderewskiundated (Box 232)
      - Parker, Theodoreundated (Box 232)
      - Phelps, A.A.undated (Box 232)
      - Sturge, Josephundated (Box 232)
      - "Watch Meeting-Waiting for the Hour," 31 Dec 1862 (Box 232)
      - Unidentifiedundated (Box 232)
    - Buildings and landscapes
      - Llewelyn Parkundated (Box 232)
      - Roxburyundated (Box 232)
      - Wiannoundated (Box 232)
      - Miscellaneousundated (Box 232)
- SERIES VIII. MEMORABILIA 1694-1984
  - Family
    - Character analysis 1913-50, undated (Box 233, Folder 1)
    - Gamesundated (Box 233, Folder 2)
    - Garrison hands project2001- (Box 233, Folder 3)
    - Valentines and greeting cardsundated (Box 233, Folder 4)
    - Numerology and metaphysics 1922-26, undated (Box 233, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous and unidentified 1847-1954, undated (Box 233, Folder 6)
    - Household lists, accounts, cookbooks and recipes
      - "Mrs. Lovell," 1694 (Box 234)
      - "Mrs. Pearson of Bath," undated (Box 234)
      - "Elizabeth Spencer," undated (Box 234)
      - "Hookes accounts" 1834 (Box 234)
      - Loose recipesundated (Box 234)
      - Unidentifiedundated (Box 234)
      - "Thomas Fuller" 1761 (measures and accounts) (Box 235)
      - "Thomas Leles" (?)
        - 1807 (Arithmetic primer) (Box 235)
        - 1810 (cookbook) (Box 235)
      - "Mary Ashby Stettam" 1832 (Box 235)
      - "Mrs. McDonald the Cook and Mrs. Hewitts the Baker," undated (Box 235)
      - "Mrs. Charles Smith," undated (Box 235)
    - Bliss, Edith ("Yoy") Lloyd Garrison
      - School notes 1929-34 (Box 236, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous 1927-40, undated (Box 236, Folder 2)
    - Emerson, Claire ("Tita") Garrison 1909-50, undated (Box 236, Folder 3)
    - Garrison
      - Agnes
        - Autograph book 1879 (Box 236, Folder 4)
        - Boston Art Students' Association 1893-1900, undated (Box 236, Folder 5)
        - Collected verse 1884-1942, undated (Box 236, Folder 6)
        - Grundmann's Studio 1897-99, undated (Box 236, Folder 7)
        - Notebooks 1932-42 (Box 236, Folder 8)
        - Official documents 1902, 1914 (Box 236, Folder 9)
        - Riddlesundated (Box 236, Folder 10)
        - Miscellaneous 1866, 1890, undated (Box 236, Folder 11)
      - Alice O'Reilly 1943-46, 1966, undated (Box 236, Folder 12)
      - David Lloyd
        - Art
          - Paintings and drawings 1918-26, undated (Box 237, Folder 1)
          - Notes 1948-87 (Box 237, Folder 2)
        - Birding
          - Index cards 1918-19 (Box 238, Folder 1)
          - Notebooks (Box 238)
          - Birds of Western Lorrainecirca 1936 (Box 238, Folder 2)
          - European Birds 1942-45 (Box 238, Folder 3-4)
          - Bird records 1944-84 (Box 238, Folder 5-8)
          - Scrapbooksundated (Box 239, Folder 1-2)
          - Miscellaneous 1900-46, undated (Box 239, Folder 3)
        - Color relationship chartsundated (Box 240, Folder 1)
        - J.H. Emerson Co. 1934-64, undated (Box 240, Folder 2)
        - Harvard
          - Instrumental Club 1926-28 (Box 240, Folder 3)
          - Miscellaneous 1924-37, undated (Box 240, Folder 4)
        - Juvenilia 1914-15, undated (Box 240, Folder 5)
        - Military papers
          - Official documents 1941-45 (Box 240, Folder 6)
          - Public Relations Office 1944-45 (Box 240, Folder 7)
          - Miscellaneous 1941-47, undated (Box 240, Folder 8)
        - Notes
          - Gift, card, and correspondence lists 1928-76, undated (Box 240, Folder 9)
          - School 1923-26, undated (Box 240, Folder 10)
          - Miscellaneous 1926-49, undated (Box 240, Folder 11)
        - Official documents 1925, undated (Box 241, Folder 1)
        - Pagan Bray Country Clubundated (Box 241, Folder 2)
        - Travel notebooks 1947-85 (Box 241, Folder 3-4)
        - Miscellaneous 1924-68, undated (Box 241, Folder 5)
      - Edith Stephenson
        - European Trip 1926 (Box 242, Folder 1)
        - Faelton Pianoforte School 1891-1900 (Box 242, Folder 2)
        - Gift lists 1901-63 (Box 242, Folder 3)
        - Invitations
          - Harvard 1895-99 (Box 242, Folder 4)
          - Miscellaneous 1893-1901, undated (Box 242, Folder 5)
        - Notebooks
          - Phone and address 1960s (Box 242, Folder 6)
          - Miscellaneous 1950-52, undated (Box 242, Folder 7)
        - Official documents 1926-36 (Box 242, Folder 8)
        - Miscellaneous 1885-1954, undated (Box 242, Folder 9)
      - Eleanor 1904-06, undated (Box 242, Folder 10)
      - Ellen Wright
        - Hair collection 1848-1911, undated (Box 243)
        - Deeds 1903-1915 (Box 244, Folder 1)
        - Notes 1874-1902 (Box 244, Folder 2)
        - Paper dollsundated (Box 244, Folder 3)
        - Miscellaneous 1840-1911, undated (Box 244, Folder 4)
      - Francis Jackson 1892-1904, undated (Box 244, Folder 5)
      - Frank Wright 1892-1960, undated (Box 244, Folder 6)
      - George Anthony ("Nickie") 1948 (Box 244, Folder 7)
      - Helen Benson 1871-76, undated (Box 244, Folder 8)
      - John Bright 1909-74 (Box 244, Folder 9)
      - Lloyd Kirkham 1895-1921, undated (Box 244, Folder 10)
      - Lucy McKim 1848-65, undated (Box 244, Folder 11)
      - Rhodes 1908 (Box 244, Folder 12)
      - Robert Linn 1959-61 (Box 244, Folder 13)
      - Theresa Holmes 1883 (Box 244, Folder 14)
      - Wendell Holmes 1913 (Box 244, Folder 15)
      - Wendell Phillips 1863-67, undated (Box 244, Folder 16)
      - William Lloyd (1805)
        - Address book listing donations to fugitive slavesundated (Box 245, Folder 1)
        - Autopsy report 1879 (Box 245, Folder 2)
        - Rockledge deeds and mortgages 1853-64 (Box 245, Folder 3)
        - Miscellaneous 1879, undated (Box 245, Folder 4)
      - William Lloyd (1838)
        - Collected verseundated (Box 245, Folder 5-8)
        - Guestbook for 70th Birthday Party 1908 (Box 245, Folder 9)
        - Handwriting analysisundated (Box 246, Folder 1)
        - Life insurance policies 1903-06 (Box 246, Folder 2)
        - Notebook of writings from Osterville tea 1877, [See also SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES - Osterville] (Box 246, Folder 3)
        - Miscellaneous 1853-93, undated (Box 246, Folder 4)
      - William Lloyd (1874) (1838)
        - Collected material
          - Jokes 1919-31, undated (Box 247, Folder 1)
          - Quotes 1925-40, undated (Box 247, Folder 2)
          - Verse
            - Loose 1900-45 (Box 247, Folder 3)
            - Notebook 1884-43, undated (Box 247, Folder 4)
          - Guestbook 1910-66 (Box 247, Folder 5)
        - Harvard, [See also SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES - Harvard University]
          - Grades 1895-96 (Box 248, Folder 1)
          - Scrapbook 1888-1903 (Box 248, Folder 2-3)
          - Yearbook 1897 (Box 248, Folder 4)
          - Miscellaneous 1893-1931 (Box 248, Folder 5)
        - Juvenilia. 1883, undated (Box 249, Folder 1)
        - Life insurance 1912-27, [See also Flat Files] (Box 249, Folder 2)
        - Official documents 1908-44 (Box 249, Folder 3)
        - Roxbury Latin School 1889-93 (Box 249, Folder 4)
        - Travel
          - Britain 1897 (Box 249, Folder 5)
          - Europe 1926 (Box 249, Folder 6)
        - Wedding guest lists 1901 (Box 249, Folder 7)
        - Miscellaneous 1888-1947, undated (Box 249, Folder 8)
      - William Lloyd 1902
        - Blindness 1952-55, undated (Box 249, Folder 9)
        - Country Day School 1920, [See also SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES] (Box 249, Folder 10)
        - Official documents 1922-51 (Box 249, Folder 11)
        - Miscellaneous 1929-58 (Box 249, Folder 12)
    - Harwood, Faith Garrisonundated (Box 250, Folder 1)
    - Norton, Katherine Garrison 1886-1908, undated (Box 250, Folder 2)
    - Villard, Oswald Garrison 1903-1942 (Box 250, Folder 3)
    - Villard, Oswald Garrison Jr. 1942 (Box 250, Folder 4)